tatamifightwear.com 2019-02-12

# Privacy – Tatami Fightwear Ltd.

Who are we?

Tatami Fightwear is the trading name of Tatami Fightwear Limited, registered in England & Wales, company no. **06923985**. Our registered office is: Unit 19-20 Endeavour Close Purcell Ave, Port Talbot, SA12 7PT. All business correspondence should be sent to Tatami Fightwear Limited Unit 19-20 Endevaour Close Purcell Ave Port Talbot SA12 7PT.

Our registered VAT number is **993665461**.

Data protection

References in this section to:

\- “Data Protection Law” means the Data Protection Act 1998 and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003, as amended from time to time, and all other applicable privacy and data protection laws and regulations, as well as any guidance and/or codes of practice issued from time to time by the Information Commissioner; and

\- “Personal Data”, “Data Controller” and “Data Processor” and “processing” shall have the meanings given under applicable Data Protection Law.

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, we (Tatami Fightwear Limited) are the Data Controller and therefore we are responsible for, and control the processing of, your Personal Data in accordance with Data Protection Law. “Personal Data” has a legal definition but, in brief, it refers to information from which a living person can be identified. Such information must be protected in accordance with Data Protection Law.

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, participate in another site feature, or otherwise deal with us in relation to the site and/or our goods and services. When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes. Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, use certain other site features or otherwise deal with us in the following ways:

\- To identify you and manage any accounts you hold with us.

\- To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

\- To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

\- To quickly process your transactions.

\- To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

\- To notify you of any changes to our website or to our services that may affect you.

\- To improve our services.

If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.

How do we protect visitor information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive information (including payment and credit information) you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.

Do we use "cookies"?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate, anonymised data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors through analysis of this aggregate, anonymised data. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.

Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include Tatami Fightwear. We may disclose your information to our own service providers, including website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential and process it only in accordance with our instructions. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

How can you opt-out or access, remove or modify information you have provided to us?

To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section, or follow the unsubscribe instructions in any marketing email you receive from us. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production. To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.

You can require us to correct any mistakes in your information which we hold free of charge. If you would like to do this, please let us know by writing to us by post or email using the contact details below.

You can request a copy of your information which we hold (this is known as a subject access request). If you would like a copy of some or it, please email, call or write to us including proof of your identity and address and let us know the information you want a copy of, including any account or reference numbers, if you have them. We may charge a small fee (currently £10) for this service.

Third party links

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).

Changes to our policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on 26th May 2017.

Questions and feedback

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.

Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](http://tatamifightware.dev.visualsoft.co.uk/terms-conditions-i7) section at www.tatamifightwear.com/pages/termsandconditions which establishes the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website, as well as our terms of use for customers.

Your consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Contact

If you have any questions please feel free to contact us by email at info@tatamifightwear.com or by writing to us at:

Tatami Fightwear LTD,

Unit 19-20,

Endeavour Close,

Purcell Ave,

Port Talbot,

SA12 7PT,

United Kingdom

Alternatively, you may prefer to pick up the phone to speak to one of our representatives on 01639 898888. Our representatives are available during the hours below: Monday to Friday: 9:30am-4:30pm
